# Trevor de Koekkoek

### Summary

A skilled and detail-oriented problem solver. Excellent written and verbal skills. Can work well in a team environment or independently and can lead a team or serve as a mentor for junior developers. Has developed numerous web and thick-client applications involving the full software development life-cycle.

Advanced skills in HTML5 / Javascript client applications using AngularJS, JQuery, KnockoutJS, Sencha Touch, Sencha ExtJS, KendoUI and JQuery UI.

Experienced in the latest Microsoft technologies including ASP.NET MVC, LINQ, Web API, Generics, Entity Framework, Code First, migrations.

Experienced in object oriented design and design patterns including MVC, Repository and MVVM.

Code versioning using Git, Mercurial, SVN and TFS.

Experienced in CSS,Twitter Bootstrap, .LESS and responsive design.

## **Work Experience**

Current, from December 2014

#### **INPO**

### Senior UI Developer

Developing a resource scheduler application for the operation of nuclear power plants. The application is developed in AngularJS, WebAPI, TypeScript, Breeze and KendoUI

Current, from June 2014

#### Benny Advantage Consultant

Developed a robust web portal for a medical application. The portal is used to do bulk updates to Parse.com via excel spreadsheets. The application is built using AngularJS, Entity Framework, and the C# Parse SDK. The application inter-operates with Parse.com and is hosted on Azure.

June 2014 – November 2014

# Bridge2 Solutions *UI Architect*

Built travel and rewards application using AngularJS, Bootstrap, angular-ui, ui-router, JSP, CSS, .LESS, JQuery, NodeJS, Grunt.

The application utilizes several webservices for searching for hotels, flights, car rentals and cruises and viewing details and adding these items to a shopping cart. Items can be purchased via accumulated rewards points.

October 2011 - January 2012

Turner Broadcasting Senior Software Consultant



#### Education

1980 - 1987

**BS**Mathematics
University of Southern Mississippi